hey people this is mithil it has
mustache icsa bank industrial credit and
investment corporation of india to begin
with company worldview indialo ic aci
largest private sector bank retail small
and medium-sized enterprises and
corporate customers financial products
and servicing offers
a bank challa branches atms another
touch point tonight coming to industry
take passengers
securities primary dealership 100 person
ics security is 25 percent
icici potential asset management 51
percent icici lombard general insurance
52 person icsa potential life insurance
51 person
presently bank in yellow five thousand
advantages and fifteen twenty eight amc
upgrade where thirty percent of the
branches are located in metro cities
launch record just contained more than
forty nine percent
rural launch fifteen percent vehicle
launch foreign person personal loans ten
person
business banking eight person credit
cards four
share of twenty five point seven percent
coming to financials revenue five twenty
two low one lakh fifty seven thousand
five thirty six percent compared to five
twenty one around two point four percent
decrease in the profits after twenty two
low twenty five thousand one ten crores
in the compared to efficient one around
36.5 percent increasing net worth effort
only too long one lakh 82 2052 crossing
compared to f51 around 15.5 percent
ingredient
or financial discount a bank fight
effect until about
company delivered good profit growth of
19.7 percent five years internet income
has gone on a daily rate of 12.5 percent
conscious contact company has low
interest quality ratio
company delivered poor sales worth of
9.3 percent
company has lower volume of twelve point
seven percent
contingent level discount thirty lakhs
hundreds of money personality company
might be capitalizing the interest cost
endings include another income of sixty
two thousand eight eighty three crores
is
to fundamentals market calculation five
lakh six not eight gross industry p
eighteen point one p e is nine point
nine people ratio two point eight book
value two six two rupees that two
increased zero point eight nine percent
at non-equity 14.79
operating performance 13.9 percent five
year sales yeah nine point thirty eight
percent ebitda thirty four down to forty
one rupees one year return twelve point
forty three percent
dividend zero point twenty one percent
five essentially return
forty five percent only past finance
twelve point four percent past six
months minus five percent past one month
one point two percent shareholding
pattern day five forty three point nine
percent mutual funds eight point eight
percent public 14.3 percent d a twelve
point eight percent
so that's all for animals of ici bank
thank you
you